{
    "subject": "resource/Ferdinand_Philippe,_Duke_of_Orl\u00e9ans",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "French prince of the house of Orl\u00e9ans",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand Philippe, Duke of Orl\u00e9ans is a French prince of the house of Orl\u00e9ans.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9392558932304382,
            "question": "Where was Ferdinand Philippe, Duke of Orl\u00e9ans from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9369584918022156,
            "question": "What is Ferdinand Philippe, Duke of Orl\u00e9ans known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8274392485618591,
            "question": "To which royal house does Ferdinand Philippe belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6378255486488342,
            "question": "Was Ferdinand Philippe a member of the French nobility?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5984290838241577,
            "question": "What was Ferdinand Philippe's role in French history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5467871427536011,
            "question": "Are there any notable descendants of Ferdinand Philippe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5245177149772644,
            "question": "What are some important facts about Ferdinand Philippe's lineage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5034075975418091,
            "question": "What title did Ferdinand Philippe hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40266624093055725,
            "question": "Can you name any significant events related to Ferdinand Philippe's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3724486529827118,
            "question": "Who were Ferdinand Philippe's parents?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand Philippe, Duke of Orl\u00e9ans is a French prince of the house of Orl\u00e9ans.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2157_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any significant events related to Ferdinand Philippe's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2157_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title did Ferdinand Philippe hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2157_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important facts about Ferdinand Philippe's lineage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2157_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2157_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Ferdinand Philippe, Duke of Orl\u00e9ans is a French prince of the House of Orl\u00e9ans.\" They mention his status as the eldest son and heir to the House of Orl\u00e9ans, his title as Prince Royal, and his birth in France, all of which are consistent with him being a French prince from that royal house."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}